Philip M. Sheppard Papers 1911-1976 1940-1976 Mss.Ms.Coll.65
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1946-1983; 28 boxes, 14 lin. feet
  - Knowles, Vincent, 1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Knudsen, John P. (Box Series I-14)
  - Koerber, Thomas, 1952-1953 (Box Series I-14)
  - Komai, Taku, 1951-1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Korn, E., 1969 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kornberg, H. L., 1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Krebs, H. A., 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Krevans, Julius R. (Box Series I-14)
  - Krickler, David M. (Box Series I-14)
    - See also Ser. I. Price Evans, David A.
  - Krimbas, Costas B., 1967-1968; 5.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Conferences and symposia; Genetics -- Polymorphism; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
  - Kubickova, Z., 1966 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kuyten, P., 1953-1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lacey, Howard C., 1975-1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lack, David, 1960-1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - La Cour, L. F., 1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lalley, Frances, 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lamotte, Maxime, 1952-1953, 1971-1972 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lancashire and Cheshire Entomological Society, 1962 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lancet, 1957-1962, 1972 (Box Series I-14)
    - See als Ser. I. Wiener, Alexander S.
  - Langmaid, Helen, 1966 (Box Series I-14)
  - Langman, Michael J. S. (Box Series I-14)
  - Langridge, John, 1972 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lanyon, P. C. H., 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - Laroca, Sebastiao, 1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lassman, Diane, 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Latimer, B., 1972 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lawrence, Michael J., 1962-1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Leao, Aristides Azevedo Pacheco, 1970-1972 (Box Series I-14)
    - See also Royal Society
  - Lear, E., 1953-1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Leddy, T., 1972 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lee, Lee-Yin, 1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lees, David R., 1966-1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lees, F. H., 1952 (Box Series I-14)
  - Leggate, J. M., 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lehane, D., 1972 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lehmann, Hermann, 1972, 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lejuez, R., 1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lempke, B. J., n.d. (Box Series I-14)
    In French
  - Lennes, Georges, 1960-1962 (Box Series I-14)
  - Leonard, Waarren H., 1953-1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lerner, I. Michael (Isadore Michael), 1962-1971; 8.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    - See also Ser. I. Evolution
    Invitations; Solicitations for support or contribution -- University of California, Berkeley; Teaching -- University of California, Berkeley; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Levene, Howard (Box Series I-14)
    - See also Ser. I. Zimmerman, David
  - Leverhulme Research Awards, 1969-1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Levin, Eve D. M., 1968, n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Levine, Philip, 1958, 1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - Levins, Richard, 1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Levitan, Max, 1956, 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lewin, S., 1966 (Box Series I-14)
    - See also Ser. I. Angseesing, Joseph
  - Lewis, Daniel (Box Series I-14)
    - See also Ser. I. Genetical Society
    - See also Ser. I. Science Progress
  - Lewis, Geoffrey, 1965-1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lewis, Trevor, 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lewontin, Richard C., 1955-1973; 15.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    - See also Ser. I. Royal Society. Aldabra Research Committee (1969-1970)
    Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Drosophila genetics; Educational matters; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Kimura, Motoo; Population genetics; Publication; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Leytham, G. W. H., 1969 (Box Series I-14)
  - Li, C. C., 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - Libby, William J., 1969-1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lieftinck, M. A., 1953-1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Life (Magazine), 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lightfoot, Jack, 1959-1960 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lilly, Lorna J., 1960, 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lindsay, D. B., 1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Linnean Society of London, 1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - Linskill, Christopher, 1973 (Box Series I-14)
  - Linsley, E. Gordon, 1953 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lints, F. A., 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lisker, Ruben, 1974, 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lissmann, H. W., 1956, 1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Liu, Chih-Chung, 1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - Liverpool (England). Parks and Recreation Department, 1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Liverpool Area Health Authority, 1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - Livingstone, E. and S., 1971 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lloyd, Monte, 1955 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lloyd, Selwyn, 1967 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lloyds Bank Ltd., 1957--1958 (Box Series I-15)
    Dumbell, Stanley
    Marr, John W.
  - Loftus, C., 1968 (Box Series I-15)
  - Logos Press, 1960-1968 (Box Series I-15)
  - Loizos, Caroline, 1966 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lomer, R. A., 1974-1975 (Box Series I-15)
  - London (England). Lord Mayor, 1975 (Box Series I-15)
  - London School of Economics and Political Science. Higher Educations Research Unit, 1969-1970 (Box Series I-15)
  - Longman Group Ltd. (Box Series I-15)
  - Lorenz, Kenneth G., 1966 (Box Series I-15)
  - Loritz, Jean, 1951 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lorkovic, Z., 1954-1960 (Box Series I-15)
    - See also Ser. I. Clarke, Cyril A. (n.d.)
  - Loughnane, Geraldine, 1966, 1968 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lovelace, Perry, 1970 (Box Series I-15)
  - Luck, C. P., 1959 (Box Series I-15)
  - Lugg, J. W. H., 1972-1974 (Box Series I-15)
    American Journal of Physical Anthropology
  - McCarthy, Kevin, 1968 (Box Series I-15)
  - McClelland, G. A. H., 1959-1971 (Box Series I-15)
  - McConnell, Richard B., 1955-1971; 46.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-15)
    - See also Ser. I. Ceppellini, R.
    - See also Ser. I. Fraser Roberts, John
    - See also Ser. I. Mehigen, J. A.
    - See also Ser. I. Schrager, G. R.
    Cancer, chemotherapy; Clarke, Cyril Astley; Conferences and symposia; Dunn, Leslie Clarence; Human genetics; Human genetics -- Blood groups; Mayr, Ernst; Publication; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - McCue, Robert, 1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - McCullough, Margaret, 1975-1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - McDermid, E. Michael, 1959-1964 (Box Series I-15)
  - MacDonald, Alex H., 1954 (Box Series I-15)
  - MacDonald, D. W., 1972-1973 (Box Series I-15)
  - Macdonald, K., 1954, 1956 (Box Series I-15)
  - Macdonald, W. W. (Box Series I-15)
    Abdulali, Salman
    Clarke, Cyril A. (1970)
    Grab, B.
    Gratz, Norman G.
    Hocking, K. S.
    Journal of Animal Ecology
    Manuila, A.
    Moles, S.
    Pant, C. P.
    Tont, Robert J.
    Wright, J. W.
    - See also Ser. I. Tonn, Robert J.
    - Folder #1, 1965-1967 (Box Series I-15)
    - Folder #2, 1968-1969 April (Box Series I-15)
    - Folder #3, 1969 May-1974 (Box Series I-15)
  - McDonald, William A., 1956-1957 (Box Series I-15)
  - McDunnough, J. H., 1953 (Box Series I-15)
  - Macfadyem, Amyen, 1968 (Box Series I-15)
  - Macfarlane, W. (Box Series I-15)
    - See Ser. I. Harper, John L.
  - McGraw-Hill Book Co., 1968-1974 (Box Series I-15)
  - McGee-Russell, S. M., 1962 (Box Series I-15)
  - McGugan, B. M., 1957-1958 (Box Series I-15)
  - McKendrick, Olive, 1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - McKusick, Victor A., 1976 (Box Series I-15)
  - McLaren, Anne, 1965-1975 (Box Series I-15)
  - LacLean, J. A. R., 1956 (Box Series I-15)
  - McLeod, L., 1965-1966, 1975 (Box Series I-15)
  - Macmillan, ?, 1959 (Box Series I-15)
  - MacMillan and Co., Ltd., 1963 (Box Series I-15)
  - MacMullen, ?, 1953 (Box Series I-15)
  - McNeil, Crichton, 1961 (Box Series I-15)
  - MacNicholas, J., 1967 (Box Series I-15)
  - McO[?]var, P. B. (Box Series I-15)
  - McPhail, J. Don, 1970 (Box Series I-15)
  - McWhirter, Kennedy G., 1957-1973 (Box Series I-15)
  - Macaulay, Dorothy (Box Series I-15)
    See oversize
  - Macefield, A. John, 1967-1974 (Box Series I-15)
  - Mackie, George O., 1956, n.d. (Box Series I-15)
  - Madden, J. S., 1966-1967 (Box Series I-15)
  - Maddock, S., 1966 (Box Series I-15)
  - Maessen, Rev. (Box Series I-15)
  - Maggiori, Gloria, 1971-1972 (Box Series I-15)
  - Main, David M., 1958 (Box Series I-15)
  - Mainx, Felix, 1959 (Box Series I-15)
  - Maisel, Herbert, 1965 (Box Series I-15)
  - Makielski, Sally K., 1967-1969 (Box Series I-15)
  - Mallet, James, 1975 (Box Series I-15)
  - Man (Journal), 1959 (Box Series I-15)
  - Mandel, Stephen P. H., 1958, 1968 (Box Series I-15)
  - Manly, Bryan F. J., 1968-1970 (Box Series I-15)
  - Manning, Aubrey, 1956-1975 (Box Series I-15)
  - Mansfield, Philip R. A., 1957-1960; 32.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-15)
    Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Invitations; Travel -- Africa
  - Manuila, A., 1969 (Box Series I-15)
  - Mariana, Mario, 1952 (Box Series I-15)
    Ford, E. B.
  - Marien, Dan, 1968 (Box Series I-15)
  - Marr, John W., 1958, 1967 (Box Series I-15)
    - See also Ser. I. Lloyds Bank Ltd.
  - Martin, Lloyd, 1953 (Box Series I-15)
  - Mason, W. R. M., 1964 (Box Series I-16)
  - Masterman, John C., 1954-1965 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mather, Kenneth, 1954-1969 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mather, Wharton B., 1967 (Box Series I-16)
  - Matheson, J. A. L., 1967 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mattingly, Peter F., 1959-1964 (Box Series I-16)
    - See also Ser. I. Freeman, Paul
  - Mattoni, R. H. T. (Box Series I-16)
  - May, E. C., 1972 (Box Series I-16)
  - Maycock, W. d'A., 1965 (Box Series I-16)
  - Maynard Smith, John, 1956, 1965-1974 (Box Series I-16)
    - See also Ser. I. O'Donald, Peter
  - Mayo, Jean, 1967 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mayo, Oliver, 1968-1972 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mayr, Ernst, 1953-1969; 21.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-16)
    Ferguson, E. A.
    - See also Ser. I. Kimura, Motoo
    Clarke, Cyril Astley; Ford, Edmund Brisco; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Genetics -- Snails; Human genetics -- Blood groups; Population genetics
  - Mead, ?, 1958 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mead, A. P., 1957 (Box Series I-16)
  - Medawar, Peter B., 1956-1974 (Box Series I-16)
  - Medical and Scientific Committee for Soviety Jewry, 1974-1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - Medical Research Council (Box Series I-16)
    - Folder #1, 1968-1972 (Box Series I-16)
    - Folder #2, 1973 Jan.-Mar. (Box Series I-16)
    - Folder #3, 1973 Apr.-Oct. (Box Series I-16)
    - Folder #4, 1974 (Box Series I-16)
    - Folder #5, 1975-1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - Medler, John T., 1960 (Box Series I-16)
  - Meeuse, A. D. J., 1964 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mehigan, J. A., 1954 (Box Series I-16)
  - Meihle, R. D., 1958 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mellanby, Kenneth, 1968 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mercer, J. A., 1966 (Box Series I-16)
  - Mercer, Rosemary, 1967 (Box Series I-16)
  - Merrel, D. J., 1956 (Box Series I-16)
  - Metcalfe, R. John A., 1961, 1966 (Box Series I-16)
  - Methuen and Co., Ltd., 1968-1969 (Box Series I-16)
  - Meyerriecks, A. J., 1962 (Box Series I-16)
  - Meyers, E. G., 1961 (Box Series I-16)
  - Micklem, H. S., 1955 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mikkola, Kauri, 1973-1976 (Box Series I-17)
  - Milani-Comparetti, Marco, 1962 (Box Series I-17)
  - Milburn, T. Robert, 1974 (Box Series I-17)
  - Miles, Hamish, 1974 (Box Series I-17)
  - Milkman, Roger D., 1965-1966 (Box Series I-17)
  - Miller, P. L., 1967 (Box Series I-17)
  - Miller, R. E., 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Miller, William C., 1964 (Box Series I-17)
  - Millon, Robert, 1952 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mills, C. P. J., 1967 (Box Series I-17)
    - See also Ser. I. Dransfield, J. W.
  - Mills, James A., 1970 (Box Series I-17)
  - Milton, J. M., 1973 (Box Series I-17)
  - Ministry of Agriculture, Fisheries and Food, 1952; 1973-76 (Box Series I-17)
  - Ministry of Defence. Procurement Office, 1973 (Box Series I-17)
  - Ministry of Housing & Local Government, 1962 (Box Series I-17)
  - Ministry of Overseas Development., 1968 (Box Series I-17)
    Science and Technology Dept.
  - Ministry of Technology, 1969 (Box Series I-17)
  - Minns, Francis C., 1963 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mirando, E. H., 1974 (Box Series I-17)
  - Molecular Biology and Radiobiology Course Secretariat, 1973 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moles, S., 1966 (Box Series I-17)
    See also Ser.I, Macdonald, W.W.
  - Molinas, M., 1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mollal, Shake Alam, 1964 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mollison, P. L., 1959-68 (Box Series I-17)
  - Molloy, Veronica M., 1966 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moment, Gairdner B., 1962-63 (Box Series I-17)
  - Monro, John, 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Monroe, [?], 1958 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mood, Eric W., 1972 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moodie, G. E. E., 1971 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moodie, Mary E., 1956 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moody, Enid, 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moor, D. C., 1955-56 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moor-Jankowski, Jan K., 1956-58 (Box Series I-17)
    See also Ser.I, Clarke, Cyril A.
  - Moore, John A., 1958-63 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moore-Rinvolucri, N. [?], n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Moorhead, [?] (Box Series I-17)
  - More O'Ferrall, Gerald J., 1970-71 (Box Series I-17)
  - Morgan, P. D., 1971 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mori, J. R. (Box Series I-17)
    See Ser.I, Thorne, Fred
  - Morin, I. O. M., 1956; n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Moriwaki, Daigoro, 1967-69 (Box Series I-17)
  - Morrell, Roy, 1958 (Box Series I-17)
  - Morris, Desmond, 1956;1965-66 (Box Series I-17)
    Gait, N.H.
  - Morris, Trevor, 1965 (Box Series I-17)
  - Morton, Newton E. (Box Series I-17)
  - Mosteiro, F. Teodoro, 1952 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mottershead, G. S., 1960; 1972-73 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mountford, Brenda, 1970-75 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mountford, James F., n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Mourant, A. E., 1954-61 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moureau, P., 1961 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mowe, B., 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Moynihan, Martin H., 1965-72 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mudie, Malcolm S., 1970 (Box Series I-17)
  - Muir, Kenneth, 1964 (Box Series I-17)
  - Mukerji, Durgadas, n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Muldivo Ltd., 1970 (Box Series I-17)
  - Muller, Gerardo Lamas, 1973 (Box Series I-17)
  - Munro Fox, H., 1956-58 (Box Series I-17)
  - Murphey's Ranches, 1969 (Box Series I-17)
  - Murphy, Deborah, n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Murray, [?] (Box Series I-17)
  - Murray, E[lizabeth], 1961-62 (Box Series I-17)
  - Murray, J. J., Jr., 1959-76 (Box Series I-17)
  - Murray, N. M., 1966 (Box Series I-17)
  - Murray, Neil, 1970; 1976 (Box Series I-17)
  - Murray, [T. J. ], n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Murty, B. R., 1965; 1973 (Box Series I-17)
  - Muspratt, Vera M., 1952-55 (Box Series I-17)
  - Muyshondt, A. (Box Series I-17)
  - Myerscough, Christopher, 1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - Myles Wright, H., 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Nabour, Robert K., 1954 (Box Series I-17)
  - Nageswara Rao N., 1975 (Box Series I-17)
  - Nash, D., 1960 (Box Series I-17)
  - National Research Council, 1959 (Box Series I-17)
  - NATO (North Atlantic Treaty Org. ), 1971 (Box Series I-17)
  - Natural Environment Research Council (Box Series I-17)
    See also Ser.II, Natural Environment Research Council. See also oversized
    - Folder #1, 1971-73 (Box Series I-17)
    - Folder #2, 1974-75 (Box Series I-17)
    - Folder #3, 1976 (Box Series I-17)
  - Nature, 1951-75 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nature Conservancy, 1954; 1960-65 (Box Series I-18)
  - Naylor, Ernest, 1972 (Box Series I-18)
    Butler, Roy; Nuffield Foundation
    See also Ser. I, Nuffield Foundation
  - Naylor, M. N. (Box Series I-18)
  - Needham, A. E. (Bob), 1970 (Box Series I-18)
  - Neil, Douglas, 1965-[66] (Box Series I-18)
  - Nelson, J. Michael, 1951 (Box Series I-18)
  - Thomas Nelson & Sons Ltd., Publishers, 1966;1972-73 (Box Series I-18)
    Ricklefs, Robert E.
  - Neston, Urban District Council, 1957 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nevo, Eviator, 1970 (Box Series I-18)
    See also Ser.I, Karlin, Samuel
  - New Scientist, 1960-66; 1976 (Box Series I-18)
  - New Sixth, 1971 (Box Series I-18)
  - New York Zoological Society, 1963 (Box Series I-18)
  - Newman, L. Hugh, 1953-60; n.d. (Box Series I-18)
    [Kettlewell?], [H.] Bernard [D.]
  - Newth, D. R., 1957-58 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nichols, David, 1960; 1966 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nicholson, A. J., 1967 (Box Series I-18)
  - Niyaz, M. A. M., 1974 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nock, Ann E., 1966 (Box Series I-18)
  - Noel, [?], 1958 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nolte, D. J., 1962 (Box Series I-18)
  - Norbury, John W., 1965-66 (Box Series I-18)
  - North Western Universities O. & M. Unit, 1969;1975 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nowell, Peter T., 1973-75 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nuffield Foundation, 1954-1975; 4 folders (Box Series I-18)
    Berry, R.J.
    Godfrey, John
    Naylor, Ernest
    See also Ser.I, Naylor, Ernest
    Business; Clarke, Cyril Astley; Evolution; Fellowships, assistantships; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Human genetics; Human genetics -- Blood groups; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Population genetics; Radiation genetics; Research support; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - Folder #1, 1954-1961 (Box Series I-18)
    - Folder #2, 1962-1967 (Box Series I-18)
    - Folder #3, 1969-1971 (Box Series I-18)
    - Folder #4, 1972-1975 (Box Series I-18)
  - Nur, Uzi (Box Series I-18)
    See Ser.I, American Naturalist
  - O'Brien, Ray, 1963 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Connor, L. K., 1968 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Donald, Peter (Box Series I-18)
    Maynard Smith, John
    See also Ser.I, Brower. Lincoln
    - Folder #1, 1966-June 1968 (Box Series I-18)
    - Folder #2, July 1968-1975 (Box Series I-18)
  - Odriozola, Miguel, 1961-62 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Farrell, A. F., 1967 (Box Series I-18)
  - Ogah, Fidelis, 1974 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Garvey, C. P., 1970 (Box Series I-18)
  - Ogata, Tomio, 1959 (Box Series I-18)
  - Ogston, A. G. (Sandy), 1972 (Box Series I-18)
  - Ohw, Bong Kug, 1967-68 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oldroyd, Margaret, 1970 (Box Series I-18)
  - Olivetti, 1964 (Box Series I-18)
  - Olivier-Wright, Annabel, 1969 (Box Series I-18)
    See a;sp Ser.I, Clarke, Cyril A.
  - Ollerant, D., 1957 (Box Series I-18)
  - Olsen, T., 1973 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Neill, Diane Jennifer, 1975 (Box Series I-18)
  - O'Neill, Felicity, 1965 (Box Series I-18)
  - Open University, 1972;1976 (Box Series I-18)
  - Ortiz, Eugenio, n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Osaka University. Faculty of Science., 1968 (Box Series I-18)
  - Osborne, Melville, 1956 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oshima, Chozo, 1969 (Box Series I-18)
  - Osman, Abdel Hamid, 1968 (Box Series I-18)
  - Outram, Valerie A., 1970 (Box Series I-18)
  - Owen, A. R. G., 1952; 1955 (Box Series I-18)
  - Owen, Denis F., 1962-72 (Box Series I-18)
  - Owen, George, 1966 (Box Series I-18)
  - Owen, Robert, 1976 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oxford, Geoffrey Stuart, 1971-74 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oxford. City Engineer, 1953 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oxford University, 1955-56; 1970; n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Oxford University Press, 1956; 1972-75 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oxfordshire Constabulary, 1959 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oxfordshire County Council, 1954 (Box Series I-18)
  - Oyolu, C., 1957 (Box Series I-18)
  - Padley, J. S., 1976 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pagden, H. T., 1961 (Box Series I-19)
  - Page, Cynthia, 1975 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pain, Adam Nicholas, 1973-74 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pal, R., 1970 (Box Series I-19)
  - Palles-Clark, Michael, 1968 (Box Series I-19)
  - Palmgren, Pontus, 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Panchen, Alec L., 1974 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pant, C. P. (Box Series I-19)
    See Ser.I, Macdonald, W.W.
  - Parbrook, H. Derrick, n.d. (Box Series I-19)
  - Parker, A. (Mrs. ), 1972 (Box Series I-19)
  - Parker, G. A., n.d. (Box Series I-19)
  - Parker, Paul F., 1972 (Box Series I-19)
  - Parkes, A. S., 1967 (Box Series I-19)
  - Parkin, David T., 1968-76 (Box Series I-19)
  - Parr, Michael J., 1964-75 (Box Series I-19)
    Manly, B.J.F.
  - Parr, Phyllis A., 1959 (Box Series I-19)
  - Parr, R. W., 1959 (Box Series I-19)
  - Parry, James M., 1965-76 (Box Series I-19)
  - A. E. Parry & Co., 1960; 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Parsons, B. J., 1974 (Box Series I-19)
  - Parsons, Peter Angas, 1958; 1964-76 (Box Series I-19)
    Roper, J. Alan
    See also Ser.I, Horner,Ken
  - Parsons, Ralph W., 1968 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pasteur, Georges, 1969; 1971 (Box Series I-19)
  - Patch, Blanche, 1966 (Box Series I-19)
  - Patel, A. R. (Box Series I-19)
  - Pateman, John A., 1966 (Box Series I-19)
  - Paterson, H. E., 1958;1967-68 (Box Series I-19)
  - Patterns of Prejudice, 1969 (Box Series I-19)
  - Paulian, Renaud, 1956-57 (Box Series I-19)
    See also Ser.I. Clark, Cyril A.
  - Payne, Marjorie, 1956 (Box Series I-19)
  - Peake, J. F., 1970 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pearce, Stella, n.d. (Box Series I-19)
  - Pearl, Stewart, 1969 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pearson, Peter (Box Series I-19)
  - Pearson, Ronald, 1967; 1970;n.d. (Box Series I-19)
  - Peberdy, J. F., 1970 (Box Series I-19)
  - Peebles Brown, D. A., 1956 (Box Series I-19)
    See also Ser.I, Clarke, Cyril (1955)
  - Pembrey, Marcus, 1969 (Box Series I-19)
  - Penny, Lesley J., 1969 (Box Series I-19)
  - Penrose, L. S., 1956 (Box Series I-19)
  - Perrin, Sheila M., 1958-65 (Box Series I-19)
  - Perrins, Chris M., 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Petersen, Bjorn, 1954 (Box Series I-19)
  - Peterson, J. M., 1958 (Box Series I-19)
  - Peterson, W. D., 1971 (Box Series I-19)
  - Philippine Airways, 1966 (Box Series I-19)
  - Philippines (Box Series I-19)
    See Ser.I, Republic of the Philippines
  - Phillip, U., 1962 (Box Series I-19)
  - Phillips, David C., 1971 (Box Series I-19)
  - Phillips, John G., 1974 (Box Series I-19)
  - Phillipson, John, 1971-72 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pickering, D. C., 1960 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pickup, Pam, 1959 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pidduck, Heather G., 1970-76 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pilecki, Christine A., 1972 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pinhey, Elliot, 1957 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pitcher, Wallace S., 1967; 1970 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pitman Publishing, 1975 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pitt, H. G., 1972 (Box Series I-19)
  - Plackett, Robin L., 1959-65 (Box Series I-19)
  - Platt, Austin P., 1972-76 (Box Series I-19)
  - Plenum Publishing Co., 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Plester, Leigh S., 1964 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pobjoy, W. E., 1976 (Box Series I-19)
  - Polani, Paul E. (Box Series I-19)
  - Pollock, William (Box Series I-19)
  - Pollock, Martin R., 1964 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pontecorvo, G., 1953-74 (Box Series I-19)
  - Popescu, Christina, 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Popham, E. J., 1964; 1969-70 (Box Series I-19)
  - Porter, R. R., 1971 (Box Series I-19)
  - Post Office Engineers, 1975 (Box Series I-19)
  - Poultry World, 1949-50 (Box Series I-19)
  - Powell, Jeffrey (Box Series I-19)
    See Ser.I, Johnson, George B.
  - Powell, Jerry A., 1969 (Box Series I-19)
  - Practical Plant Genetics, n.d. (Box Series I-19)
  - Prentice/Hall International, 1972 (Box Series I-19)
  - Prescott, Timothy, 1966 (Box Series I-19)
  - Price Evans, David A., 1965-74;n.d. (Box Series I-19)
    Krickler, David M.
  - Pringle, J. W. S., 1969-70 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pritchard, G. J., 1968-74 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pritchard, R. H., 1972-73 (Box Series I-19)
  - Proctor, L., 1968 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pugh, F. G., 1873 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pumphrey, Alison, 1963 (Box Series I-19)
    Clarke, C[yril] A.
  - Pumphrey, R. J., 1956-67; n.d. (Box Series I-19)
    See also Ser.I, Ashton, G.C.
    See also Ser.I, Dumbell, Stanley
  - Punnett, R. C., 1960 (Box Series I-19)
  - Pyke, David A., n.d. (Box Series I-19)
  - Quicke, Donald L. J., 1976 (Box Series I-20)
  - Qureshi, Judith A., 1969;1971 (Box Series I-20)
  - Race, R. R., 1954-75 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ramlal, Sonny (Box Series I-20)
    See Ser.I, Emsley, Michael G.
  - Randall, P. A., 1972 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rattle, Denis G., 1974 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rawlings, J. O., 1968 (Box Series I-20)
  - Readett, M. D., 1965 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reddi, O. S., 1968 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reed, Juliet, 1858 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rees, C. J., 1970 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rees, Hugh H., 1971-76 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reeve, Eric C. R., 1975 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reeves, H. C., 1967 (Box Series I-20)
  - Regency Travel & Freight Ltd., 1971 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reilly, Conor, 1971-73 (Box Series I-20)